(Leonard:)I'm just gonna go home
and let my work speak for itself.
(Raj:)You're right. This is beneath me.
Like your mother was last night.
(Leonard:)How about it, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)What do you think I should do?
(Amy:)Well, you'll always
be an academic success...
(Amy:)...but I seriously question
whether you'll make any more friends.
Oh, I don't want any more, but let's go.
(Barry:)Are you kidding?
I would love to babysit for you.
- I could not ask you to do that.
- Nonsense, children love me.
(Barry:)Something about me
just makes them laugh and laugh.
(Leonard:)No, we cannot lose to that jerk.
- Yeah, screw it. I'm going in.
- Hold on.
"Screw it, I'm going in"
is what I said to your mother last night.